What are you talking about? I’m from the city of Khmelnitsk. Where are you from?
о чём беседуешь я из города Хмельницке
I’m from the city of Simferopol. Cool and the
откуда Я из города Симферополь Классно а
country.
страна
Which council is Russia? Which country?
Какая совет Россия Какая страна Ты что
Don’t you know? I just know there are brave people
не знаешь не я просто знаю есть смелые
who admit that it’s Ukraine. But the
которые признаются что Украина Но к ним
FSB immediately comes to them; you have some kind of
сразу ФСБ приходит у вас какой-то
Crimean SMERSH. I understand.  what you are not allowed
Крымский СМЕРШ Я понимаю что вам нельзя
to voice this is why it is good you are
Это озвучивать поэтому это хорошо ты
susceptible well susceptible to propaganda well done yes I
подвержен хорошо подвержен пропаганде
understand And you yourself Who is your
молодец да понял А вы сами Кто по
nationality by nationality I am
национальности по национальности Я
Russian Russian Where did you come from in
русский русский Откуда вы взялись в
Simferopol
Симферополе
Russian but where did the Ukrainians come from in
русский а вот откуда украинцы взялись в
Simferopol No, where exactly are you from?
Симферополе Не ну вы вы откуда конкретно
Your parents  from where you came to
вы ваши Ваши родители откуда приехали в
Simferopol in Simferopol And
Симферополь в Симферополя А родители
your parents are also Simferopol and your
ваши тоже Симферополя а бабушка и
grandparents are also Simferopol stars grandfather stars just
дедушка тоже Симферополя звезди дед
stars Well, you see You see, well, that’s
звезди просто звезди Ну вот види Вот
how Let’s say
видишь ну вот как
in what year you were born in forty-
Давайте в кам году вы родились в сорок
seven in forty-seven yes And your
седьмом в сорок седьмом да А ваши
parents under Soviet rule  yes And
родители при при Советской власти да А
your parents were born in Simferopol In
ваши родители родились в Симферополе В
what year in the eighth and in the ninth in the
каком году в восьмом и в девятом в
eighth and in the ninth Yes and
восьмом и в девятом Да а бабушка и
grandparents in Simferopol In what year oh those in
дедушка в Симферополе В каком году ой те
general in 1700 some I don’t know 1700
вообще в 1700 какой-то не знаю 1700
grandparents
бабушка и дедушка
were born about No no that’s about  great-grandfathers
родилась про Нет нет это про прадедушки
Yeah, I understand your great-grandfathers
Угу понял ваши прадедушки в 1700
were born in 1700 and in some
родились да каком-то В каком
approx. Yes, I’m
приблизительно Да это я образно
speaking figuratively long before the Russian
говорю дого ещё до того как Российская
Empire captured Crimea Yes, you have your
империя захватила Крым Да у тебя У тебя
grandmother, when was she born? Grandmother will now
бабушка-то когда родилась Бабушка сейчас
say grandmother was born in grandfather was born in the
скажу бабушка родилась в дед родился в
twenty-fifth  year, and my grandmother in thirty-
двадцать пятом году а бабушка в тридцать
eight is not in Riche Oh my God, my God
восьмом не в рише Боже мой боже мой Да
Yes, these are my parents Well, I seem to be
это мои родители Ну так и я вроде как-то
a little younger than
немножко помоложе
you, and about my grandmother And about my grandmother when I
вас а а про бабушку А про бабушку когда
gave birth, I don’t know about my grandmothers But I
родила про бабушки уже не знаю А вот
know my grandmother, I talked to her  You
бабушку знаю я с ней общался Вы же
communicated with your grandmother, it’s clear Yes, it’s clear, it’s
общались с бабушкой понятно Да понятно
clear But you can say if she
понятно А можно вот сказать если она в
was born in 1700 Yes Like, oh well, I already
1700 родилась Да Типа да ладно это я уже
told you from the lantern that you fell, that
От фонаря тебе сказал что ты припал то
is, you were yes, well, if you
есть вы было был да ну если ты так
think so, then so Well, I think yes I
считаешь Значит так Ну я считаю да
think  Well, so what? I can’t take
считаю ну ну и что Я же не могу отнять
your opinion away from you. It’s good. Where did
твоё мнение у тебя хорошо А откуда
your ancestors get to
вообще ваши предки попали в
Simferopol? How do I know where my
Симферополь я откуда я знаю откуда мои
ancestors came from and they did? Yeah, in short,
предки попали так и попали Ага короче
they lived in Simferopol for centuries, yes. Well, of
жили и поконо веков в Симферополе да Ну
course, I just understood from you.  your
естественно понял у вас просто А у вас
father
отец
fought in the Second World War Well, what a holy cause he
воевал Ну как же святое дело награждён
was awarded. Of course, let’s very simply
Был конечно Давайте очень просто
look, there is a website with all the Soviet
смотрите есть сайт со всеми советскими
awards. Now we’ll see, it was
наградами Сейчас мы посмотрим был он
Simferopol and no,
Симферополь и нет так
so we’re gaining the memory of the people. Now we’ll
так память народа набираем Сейчас мы
see. I don’t mind, yes, yes. Name it like
посмотрим Я не против да да Назовите как
your father.  name surname first name
вашего отца звали фамилия имя
patronymic Maybe I can also give you the key to the
отчество Может тебе ещё и ключ от
apartments where the money is all here and
квартир дать где деньги лежат всё вот и
Simferopol So please tell me your
Симферополь Вот скажи пожалуйста у тебя
dad fought for me not he is younger he was
папа воевал у меня не он младше он
born in the fifty-fourth year grandfather
пятьдесят четвёртого года рождения дед
fought de grandfather yes in the ass Pavel
воевал де дед да по попк Павел
Vasilyevich Yes, I’m driving him in  on sai
Васильевич Да вот я вбиваю его на сай
grandfather grandfather grandfather with whom he fought with the Germans
дед дед дед с кем воевал с немцами
fought was awarded by the Soviet Union
воевал награждён был советским союзом
here is look I go there is a site
вот есть смотри я захожу есть сайт
memory of the people Yes look at documents about the
память народа Да поиз документов об
participants in
участниках
the war No you are not Podgora grandfather Not Podgora
войны Нет ты не подгора дед Не подгора
look my
смотри мой
grandfather was awarded by the Soviet Union he
дед награждение от Советского Союза он
fought with the Germans Yes  did your dad
воевал с немцами Да а ты вот твой батя
fight or not yet again I turn off the sounds I
воевал или не ещ раз я те отключаю звуки
repeat the question Yes here I am My grandfather priest
Повторяю вопрос Да вот я Мой дед попк
Pavel Vasilyevich I can I can tell And
Павел Васильевич Я могу я могу сказать И
you can go and check on the website Yes
ты можешь зайти и на сайте проверить Да
when was he awarded what was your grandfather awarded for
когда награждён за что награждён твой
if he fought and was awarded tell me
дед если воевал и награждён скажи
his last name  patronymic name of grandfather or
фамилию имя отчество деда или
father Butuzov Vladimir Butuzov Ivan
отца Бутузов Владимир Бутузов Иван
Trofimovich
трофимович
Butuzov Ivan Ivan Trofimovich Give the date of
Бутузов Иван Иван трофимович Давай дата
birth if there is a clarifying one or you don’t
рождения если есть уточняющая или не
remember
помните
1908 now now because
1908 год сейчас сейчас по потому что
maybe not
может быть нес
so so there is 908 born
так так есть 908 года есть рождённый
Ulyanovsk region Kuzovatovsky district
Ульяновская область кузоватовский район
Kuibyshev region Kuzovatovsky
куйбышевская область кузоватовский
district Well,  how he was awarded No no no
район Ну и как награждён Нет не не так
no in Simferopol who was born
нету в Симферополе который родился
yours no
вашего нету
from So I am those awarded No no no no no
от Так я те награждён Нет нету нету нету
your father was not awarded Yes,
вашего отца не награждён Да ну вот я
well, I’m looking Let’s see Butusov Butuzov
смотрю Давайте ещ раз Бутусов Бутузов
or Butusov Butuzov awarded like that or not
или Бутусов Бутузов так награждён или не
and not Now I’ll find you  not awarded
сжд и не Сейчас я найду вам не награждён
Butuzov
Бутузов
there is no Simferopol there is no Simferopol
нету Симферополя нету Симферополя
born in 908 but
рождённого 908 года
my mother was born and not my father but
буту рождена моя мама а не папа а а папа
where was my father born You said you said in
где родил Ты же говорил ты же говорил в
Simferopol and and my dad was born in the
Симферополе а а папа рождён в
Ulyanovsk region Look, yes,
Ульяновской области Вот вот смотри да о
in the Ulyanovsk region there is, yes, yes, yes 14
в Ульяновской области есть да вот да 14
September 1908, Ulyanovsk region,
сентября 1908 года Ульяновская область
Kuzovatovsky district, village of Bayevka Yes, so he
кузоватовский район село баевка Да так
was awarded. Either he was awarded the
награждён Или так награждён или нет
Order of the Patriotic War of the second degree or not. You
орден Отечественной войны второй степени
see, there is a hero, yes, yes, a hero, Yes, a
есть Вот видишь герой есть да да герой
hero, yes. Now let’s see, by the way,
Да герой да Сейчас посмотрим кстати
now it’s not the Trans-Baikal Trans-Baikal
сейчас по не Забайкальский Забайкальский
District, he probably fought with the Japanese there
округ он с японцами наверное там воевал
Now we  Let's see now, I'll tell you straight away. The
Сейчас мы посмотрим сейчас прямо тебе
combat path is all here.
скажу Боевой путь всё тут
That is, it turns out, you
Вот то есть получается видишь ты
're pretending to be a native Crimean, but it
притворяешься коренным крымчанина а
turns out you're not from this one. Well, I
оказывается ты из этой не поди Так я же
was born there in Crimea, no, no. Wait, that
родился там в Крыму не не Подожди то
is, dad came to Crimea after the war, well,
есть папа приехал в Крым после войны ну
naturally, but mom lived  and
ну естественно а мама жила та
so we can break through mom like this and
так вот мы и маму можем пробить так и
mom seems like the truth has arrived. Everything is
мама кажется что приехала правда Всё
clear with you and grandpa, everything is like this.
ясно с тобой да деда всё вот так
Native Crimeans put a plus for
коренные крымчане поставьте плюс за
the unwinding of these indigenous Crimeans. Yes, that’s how
размот вот этих коренных крымчан Да вот
they all are, yes because
так они все да потому что
yes in the Soviet Union. Yes, they brought them to Crimea.  all of these
да в совке Да завозили в Крым вот этих
from these Ulyanovsk regions, damn
всех из этих ульяновских областей блин
Tver and all this stuff, and they brought
тверских и всякой это мухос да привозили
them, they were populated specifically in the Crimea, so that they
их заселяли специально Крым да чтобы их
were the majority of the Tatars, they were evicted, Yes, the
там было большинство татар выселяли Да
Ukrainians were evicted, and they were settled there, yes,
украинцев выселяли А их заселяли туда да
and now it sits like this,
И сейчас оно вот сидит такое Да
and the grandmother, great-grandmother, in short, in the Crimea, like, yes,
и бабушка прабабушка короче в Крыму типа
yes  yes, here it is, damn it, dude, it’s all
да да да вот оно всё блин чувак это всё
simple Yes, I can say Yes, my grandfather,
просто Да я могу сказать Да мой дед да
yes he is from the Khmelnitsky region, here from near
он с Хмельницкой области вот тут из-под
Khmelnytsky beu I go in and drive it in, you can see
Хмельницка беу я захожу вбиваю его видно
When they called up the Battle path, what did they
Когда призвали Боевой путь что там
do there, right, all the scans Yes, where was
сделал прям все сканы Да есть где
he born, yes And here  it
родился да И тут у дедушки этого
turns out that the grandfather, in short, is not from
оказывается что дед да короче не из
Simferopol, and the father is
Симферополя да
no longer the father Yes, from Ulyanovsk, yes And the
уже батя не батя Да из Ульяновска да А
mother is from Simferopol, yes, and the mother is not
мамка из Симферополя да там и мамка не
from Simferopol, yes Class Class I got
из Симферополя да Класс Класс Я получил
great pleasure from roasting
огромное удовольствие от прожарки вот
these Vatanov Yes, but this is a very
этих Ватанов Да но это очень
revealing video on purpose  Now
показательный ролик специально сейчас
I’ll say yes in a Russian summary so that
скажу да на русском резюме чтобы видели
everyone in Russia can see this is an indicator.
все в России это и есть показатель Вот
This is from time immemorial Crimea is Russian and you dung [ __ ] into
это из покон веков Крым русский да в
Crimea under the Soviet Union.
Крым При Советском Союзе
But in order to populate it
навозиш сраний Да вот для того чтобы его
with a certain number of Yes
э определённым количеством Да
Russian population, just like
российского населения так же как
they brought it to Lithuania in  Latvia to Estonia,
завозили в Литву в Латвию в Эстонию
especially to Kazakhstan, that is,
специально в Казахстан да то есть
they diluted the local population with
разбавляли местное население вот
these elements from these central
этим элементов из центральных вот этих
regions of Russia. So, very, very
регионов России Так что очень-очень
cool unwinding, I really liked it, we will
классный размотка очень понравилось мы
definitely post it as a video.
обязательно выложим это роликом
Therefore, support and comment with
Поэтому поддерживайте да коммента
likes, subscribe to my Telegram directly at
лайками подпишись на мий Telegram прямо
once axis VN
зараз ось ВН
apoc tse  more and more respectfully YouTube took
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through the skarg ODS in your ban and I do
нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
n’t show too many videos to people, I don’t
багато видео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams at all times, so for
показуе информация про стримы тому для
you we Malitative link to write right
тоб мы Мали тивный звязок пишиться прямо
away and Popik there in telegra okrim video schetezh
зараз а Попик там в телегра окрим видео
tsikava and korisna information and  we are
ще теж цикава и корисна информация и ми
sorry for you trimati postiyny
повинни з вами тримати постийний
operational link is not important in that chi
оперативный звязок не залежно в того чи
show you the process YouTube Slava ukraini
покаже вам проце YouTube Слава украини
write
пиши